{
    "id": "9de4a43d7f094a21a029dc4721b9b22e",
    "title": "Easily Confused Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The cold weather .............................. my health.",
            "description": "Affect is a verb and effect is a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "affected",
                "effected"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "224d3ae75ca243dd98617efd07bda390"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cold weather had an adverse .............................. on my health.",
            "description": "Affect is a verb and effect is a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "affect",
                "effect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2c13be24d23e42f795d7495b819a1815"
        },
        {
            "question": "Travel can be an excellent ................................. to one's education.",
            "description": "A complement is something that completes.",
            "answers": [
                "complement",
                "compliment"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee95630437d042c88169a3307947458f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hostess received glowing ............................... on the dinner.",
            "description": "A compliment is an expression of praise.",
            "answers": [
                "complements",
                "compliments"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "90920a9d076c4a76b85b29a6cc45df42"
        },
        {
            "question": "The extreme cold................................ the mountain climbers.",
            "description": "To discomfort is to make someone uncomfortable.",
            "answers": [
                "uncomforted",
                "miscomforted",
                "discomforted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4fe62b990198486e80bab93e0d22d8ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "I made ............................... inquiries about his credit rating.",
            "description": "Discreet means careful, judicious or cautious.",
            "answers": [
                "discreet",
                "discrete"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15c5fbfd29a54f64a18acfc408aa5bee"
        },
        {
            "question": "Use your own .................................. in choosing a restaurant.",
            "description": "Discretion means good judgment.",
            "answers": [
                "discreetion",
                "discretion",
                "discreation"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f5368b15d9e476e8f6828533b3eac24"
        },
        {
            "question": "Charles Dickens was an .................................. writer.",
            "description": "Eminent means illustrious.",
            "answers": [
                "eminent",
                "imminent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da14e02366424db0a15706d57cafe683"
        },
        {
            "question": "A storm is ...............................",
            "description": "Imminent means impending.",
            "answers": [
                "eminent",
                "imminent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26260db278744d0fb29d5b28037ad5ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not even the experts could figure out the magician's ............................ escape.",
            "description": "Ingenious means clever, cunning.",
            "answers": [
                "ingenious",
                "ingenuous"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d3a3dd842cdc433dab2b20f1ffa89a0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Children are more ........................................... than adults.",
            "description": "Ingenuous means open or frank.",
            "answers": [
                "ingenious",
                "ingenuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e4c667cd39d843fcb560085b1cb4c1fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ................................. credit cards here.",
            "description": "To accept is to take something offered.",
            "answers": [
                "accept",
                "agree",
                "expect"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "825a73246e2a4a6fac927b5592d997f7"
        }
    ]
}